physics = '[{"q_id" : "1" ,"question" : "Who wrote optiks?", "opt1" : "Einstein", "opt2" : "Newton" , "opt3" : "Feynman", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "2"},{"q_id" : "2","question" : "What is a Black hole?", "opt1" : "star", "opt2" : "planet" , "opt3" : "moon", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "4"},{"q_id" : "3" ,"question" : "What is x in E=mx", "opt1" : "speed of light", "opt2" : "sqaure of speed of light" , "opt3" : "Length", "opt4" : "Wavelength","answer" : "2"},{"q_id" : "4" ,"question" : "Genius is synonymous for", "opt1" : "Einstein", "opt2" : "Newton" , "opt3" : "von Neumann", "opt4" : "Turing","answer" : "1"},{"q_id" : "5" ,"question" : "Who wrote a Brief History of Time?", "opt1" : "Grindelwald", "opt2" : "Schrondinger" , "opt3" : "Dirac", "opt4" : "Hawking","answer" : "4"},{"q_id" : "6" ,"question" : "Where was Einstein born?", "opt1" : "Dubai", "opt2" : "Bombay" , "opt3" : "Germany", "opt4" : "USA","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "7" ,"question" : "Who unified Electrics and Magnetism?", "opt1" : "Abu bhai", "opt2" : "Turing" , "opt3" : "Maxwell", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "8" ,"question" : "Who discovered buoyancy?", "opt1" : "Chadwick", "opt2" : "Aristotle" , "opt3" : "Archimides", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "9" ,"question" : "Who proposed the Special Theory of Relativity?", "opt1" : "Newton", "opt2" : "Einstein" , "opt3" : "Shakespeare", "opt4" : "Ellen Degeneres","answer" : "2"},{"q_id" : "10" ,"question" : "What is a planeterium?", "opt1" : "home", "opt2" : "goodQues" , "opt3" : "goat", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "4"}]';
chemistry = '[{"q_id" : "1" ,"question" : "Which among the following is the main constituent of Biogas?", "opt1" : "Methane", "opt2" : "Propane" , "opt3" : "Butane", "opt4" : "Ethane","answer" : "1"},{"q_id" : "2","question" : "Which among the following is a Noble Gas?", "opt1" : "Nitrogen", "opt2" : "Hydrogen" , "opt3" : "Oxygen", "opt4" : "Helium","answer" : "4"},{"q_id" : "3" ,"question" : "Which among the following is responsible for depletion of Ozone?", "opt1" : "Carbon monoxide", "opt2" : "Carbon dioxide" , "opt3" : "Chlorofluoro carbon", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "4" ,"question" : "Which among the following element is an essential constituent of acids?", "opt1" : "Hydrogen", "opt2" : "Oxygen" , "opt3" : "Sulphur", "opt4" : "Nitrogen","answer" : "1"},{"q_id" : "5" ,"question" : "Who among the following had given the Atomic Theory?", "opt1" : "Benjamin Franklin", "opt2" : "Madam Curie" , "opt3" : "John Dalton", "opt4" : "Albert Einstein","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "6" ,"question" : "The nucleus of an atom consists of", "opt1" : "electrons and neutrons", "opt2" : "electrons and protons" , "opt3" : "protons and neutrons", "opt4" : "All of the above","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "7" ,"question" : "The most commonly used bleaching agent is", "opt1" : "Alcohol", "opt2" : "Chlorine" , "opt3" : "Pumpkin Juice", "opt4" : "Mud","answer" : "2"},{"q_id" : "8" ,"question" : "The most abundant rare gas in the atmosphere is", "opt1" : "He", "opt2" : "Ar" , "opt3" : "Kr", "opt4" : "Xe","answer" : "2"},{"q_id" : "9" ,"question" : "The inherited traits of an organism are controlled by", "opt1" : "RNA molecules", "opt2" : "nucleotides" , "opt3" : "DNA molecules", "opt4" : "enzymes","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "10" ,"question" : "The maximum number of covalent formed by nitrogen is", "opt1" : "1", "opt2" : "2" , "opt3" : "4", "opt4" : "3","answer" : "3"}]';
maths = '[{"q_id" : "1" ,"question" : "What is 2+3?", "opt1" : "2", "opt2" : "3" , "opt3" : "5", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "2","question" : "What is 2x6?", "opt1" : "1", "opt2" : "5" , "opt3" : "12", "opt4" : "Not computable","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "3" ,"question" : "Who amoung the following is a Mathematician?", "opt1" : "Roger Federer", "opt2" : "Lee Chong Wei" , "opt3" : "David Hilbert", "opt4" : "Virat Kohli","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "4" ,"question" : "How many words are there in this sentence?", "opt1" : "11", "opt2" : "12" , "opt3" : "14", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "4"},{"q_id" : "5" ,"question" : "Calculate 10/5", "opt1" : "1", "opt2" : "11" , "opt3" : "2", "opt4" : "tends to infinity","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "6" ,"question" : "What is the probability of getting a Head if we toss a fair coin?", "opt1" : "2/5", "opt2" : "3/5" , "opt3" : "5/11", "opt4" : "1/2","answer" : "4"},{"q_id" : "7" ,"question" : "Solve (2x4-6)/2 (Calculators NOT allowed)", "opt1" : "2", "opt2" : "1" , "opt3" : "0", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "2"},{"q_id" : "8" ,"question" : "In acronym BODMASS, B stands for", "opt1" : "Bull", "opt2" : "Badminton" , "opt3" : "Bracket", "opt4" : "none","answer" : "3"},{"q_id" : "9" ,"question" : "Who is known as the King of Mathematics?", "opt1" : "Me", "opt2" : "Leonhard Euler" , "opt3" : "Carl Fredrich Gauss", "opt4" : "David Hilbert","answer" : "2"},{"q_id" : "10" ,"question" : "What is the exact value of Pi?", "opt1" : "22/7", "opt2" : "3.14" , "opt3" : "Both 1 and 2", "opt4" : "Insufficient paper","answer" : "4"}]';
